[
    {
        "question": "This drink contains caffeine.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "Coffee",
        "choices": [
            "Mineral water",
            "Orange juice",
            "Coffee",
            "Beer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish the proverb:\n\nPoets are born, ________.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "...not made.",
        "choices": [
            "...not made.",
            "...but can also be made.",
            "...but thats not for sure.",
            "..., long live the poets!"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a TV program is rated G then this is true.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "It is suitable for all audiences.",
        "choices": [
            "It contains moderate violence.",
            "It contains mild sexual situations.",
            "It is suitable for all audiences.",
            "It is suitable for young children."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The theory of relativity was introduced in physics by this man.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "Albert Einstein",
        "choices": [
            "Galileo Galilei",
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Archimedes",
            "Isaac Newton"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The symbol for the chemical element iron is this.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "Fe",
        "choices": [
            "I",
            "Fe",
            "Zn",
            "Br"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The author of the novel A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man is this writer.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "James Joyce",
        "choices": [
            "T. S. Eliot",
            "Samuel Beckett",
            "William Faulkner",
            "James Joyce"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The capital of Mongolia is this city.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "Ulaanbaatar",
        "choices": [
            "Davao",
            "Islamabad",
            "Quezon",
            "Ulaanbaatar"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitochondrias function in cells is to perform this.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "To convert organic materials into energy",
        "choices": [
            "To control chemical reactions within the cytoplasm",
            "To store information needed for cellular division",
            "To convert organic materials into energy",
            "To process proteins targeted to the plasma membrane"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The US bought Alaska in this year.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "1867",
        "choices": [
            "1942",
            "1882",
            "1854",
            "1867"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The 23rd US President was in office during this period.",
        "category": "general",
        "answer": "1889 - 1893",
        "choices": [
            "1909 - 1913",
            "1889 - 1893",
            "1837 - 1841",
            "1877 - 1881"
        ]
    }
];